(Amy:)Sheldon,
I don't think everyone...
(Sheldon:)Wolowitz, perfect.
Everyone listen to Wolowitz.
Okay, then, uh, (clears throat)
Sheldon, (chuckles)
(Howard:)we've known each other
a long time.
(Howard:)And it is a pleasure
to work with you
(Howard:)and call you my friend.
(Sheldon:)Little generic. Keep thinking.
We'll circle back.
(Sheldon:)Wil Wheaton, go.
(Wil:)Sheldon, I know that we've had
our ups and downs,
(Wil:)but I can honestly say
(Wil:)that my life is
so much more interesting
(Wil:)because you are in it.
(Wil:)We may have met because
you are a fan of Star Trek.
(Wil:)But I have become
a fan of Sheldon Cooper.
(Wil:)Live long and prosper,
buddy.
(Wil:)And happy birthday.
ALL:
Cheers.
(Sheldon:)That's how you do it, Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)Now you see
(Sheldon:)why he's famous and you're not.
(Amy:)Sheldon,
(Beverley:)I know the future holds
great things for you,
(Beverley:)and we all can't wait to see
what they are.
(Beverley:)Happy birthday, dear.
ALL:
Cheers.
Someone call Animal Control.
There's a cougar on the loose.